<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GhoomoGyaan</string>
    <string name="mobile"> Mobile no.</string>
    <string name="otp">Send OTP</string>
    <string name="Enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="saras_baug_description">Sarasbaug is a major landmark in the city of Pune in India.[1] The place where the park now stands was once occupied by a small lake. However, the lake dried up and was later developed into Sarasbaug. The whole 25-acre (10 ha) complex is known as Sarasbaug. The Ganesh temple in Saras Baug is also known as Talyatla Ganapati (in Marathi:तळ्यातला गणपती ) which translates as the Ganapati of the lake.</string>
    <string name="shanivar_wada_description">Shaniwar Wada is a historical fortification in the city of Pune, India.Built in 1732, it was the great seat of the Peshwas of the Maratha Empire until 1818. Following the rise of the Maratha Empire, the palace became the center of Indian politics in the 18th century.</string>
    <string name="dagdushet">The Dagadusheth Halwai Ganapati temple is a Hindu Temple located in Pune and is dedicated to the Hindu god Ganesh. The temple is visited by over hundred thousand pilgrims every year.Devotees of the temple include celebrities and chief ministers of Maharashtra who visit during the annual ten-day Ganeshotsav festival. The main Ganesh idol is insured for sum of ₹10 million (US$130,000).[4] It celebrated 130 years of its Ganapati in 2022</string>
    <string name="rajiv_gadhi_garden">The Rajiv Gandhi Zoological Park, commonly known as the Rajiv Gandhi Zoo or Katraj Zoo, is located in Katraj, Pune district, Maharashtra State, India. It is managed by the Pune Municipal Corporation. The 130-acre (53 ha) zoo is divided into three parts: an animal orphanage, a snake park, and a zoo, and includes the 42-acre (17 ha) Katraj Lake.</string>
    <string name="Sinhagad" translatable="false">Sinhagad is an ancient hill fortress located at around 49 km southwest of the city of Pune, India.Previously known as Kondhana, the fort had been the site of many battles, most notably the Battle of Sinhagad in 1670.It is located in the Pune district in Maharashtra. The fort is also on the famous fort in Maharashtra which has a great history of Tanaji Malusare. The fort was captured by Tanaji Malusare and his brother. </string>
</resources>